Oh please don't let me die
Waiting for your touch
No, don't give up on life
This endless dead end
狂|<く#|る#|っ#|た時|<と#|け計|い 刻|<き#|ざむ命|<い#|の#|ち
こぼれてく記|<き憶|お#|くの砂|<す#|な
芽|<め#|生|ばえた 思|<お#|もいまで
ねえ こんなに呆|<あ気|っ#|けなく
消|<きえてしまうの
I wish I was there...
Oh, please don't let me die
Waiting for your touch
二|<に度|どと なにも 失|<なくさぬように
私|<わ#|た#|しを忘|<わ#|すれて 始|<は#|じめて
"Restart!"
No, don't give up on life
This endless dead end
君|<き#|みを砕|<く#|だくこの悲|<か#|なしみが
いつか 終|<おわりますように
For now I'll see you off
My time is spinning around
Your deep black eyes
I forgot what time it is
And our memories are gone...?
甘|<あ#|まい香|<か#|おり放|<は#|#|なつ
追|<つ#|い#|憶|お#|くと いう名|<なの罠|<わ#|な
誘|<さ#|そわれ 囚|<と#|らわれ
なぜ 抗|<あ#|な#|がえもせずまた
溺|<お#|ぼれてしまうの
I wish you were here
Oh, never close your eyes
Searching for a true fate
どこか 消|<きえた あのぬくもりを
追|<おいかけ 続|<つ#|づけて 見|<み失|<う#|し#|なう
"Restart!"
So, let us try again
From the very first time
"きっときっと" そうやって今|<い#|まも
虚|<む#|なしい 輪|<わを描|<え#|がいてる
For now, see you again
Fading in Fading out
I wish we were there
あの日|<ひ々には 戻|<も#|どれない
時|<と#|きは強|<つ#|よく 哀|<か#|なしく強|<つ#|よく
ただただ 進|<す#|すんで ゆくだけ
"Restart"
No don't give up on life
This endless dead end
振|<ふり返|<か#|#|えらない そんな強|<つ#|よさを
誰|<だ#|れも皆|<み#|な演|<え#|んじてる
For now I'll see you off
And we'll die
Waiting for a new day
二|<に度|どと...
And we'll start
Waiting for a new day
君|<き#|みと...
Oh please don't let me die
消|<きえないで ah...